http://www.technodyke.com/privacy.asp

The Gathering Place for the Web Savvy Dyke! TechnoDyke.Com!
Join the Mailing List:
Set TechnoDyke As Your Start Page!
Privacy Statement
TechnoDyke.Com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: TechnoDyke.Com.We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes, such as providing you with accurate information. Example: In the message boards, it dictates; "You last Visited - 3/29/00 3:02:44 PM" - This information was obtained by a "cookie".Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This site contains links to other sites. TechnoDyke.Com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.When you register for an email address at TechnoDyke.Com - you are in essence, registering with BigMailBox.Com - our 3rd party vendor. Any demographic information you give them is not shared with us, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of BigMailBox.Com.We do not share the information you give us with any other companies.Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Choice/Opt-OutOur site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can send email to info@technodyke.netCorrect/UpdateThis site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. email info@technodyke.netInformation SharingTechnoDyke.Com does not Give, Lend, Sell or otherwise distribute your personal information to 3rd parties.Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Stacy BiasTechnoDyke.Cominfo@technodyke.net
| About | Activism
| Advertise | Advice| Archive | Awards | Book Reviews | BookStore | Chat | Contact | Dating
| Dyke of the Month | Free Email |
Geek | Help Wanted | Horoscopes | Linkage | Message Boards | Music | News | Portland Local | Privacy | ©1999/2001 - TechnoDyke® LLC
|
All Rights Reserved
Support TechnoDyke.Com - + - Make a Donation
